Guide to the Stevens family papers, [ca. 1775-2010]
Stevens family papers, [ca. 1775-2010]
- Series VIII. Photographs
  - VIII-A. People
    - Chudy family, 1984-1991 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Clark, Charles G., 1908 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Clark(e) family, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Congressmen when Robert W.S. Stevens was in Congress: Sereno E. Payne, Bancroft Hestonian(?), Thomas F. Bayard, Sr., Lucius Q.C. Lamar, Arthur P. Gorman, John J. Ingalls, Preston B. Plumb, Thomas A. Hendricks, Augustus H. Garland, John G. Carlisle, ca.1883-1885 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Cook family, 1979, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Cormier family, 1959, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Correa, Dudley Stevens (Gregory) and family, 1920-1958, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Croll, Albert Garber and Rebecca Elmira (Ivins) (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Croll, Albert Ivins and Sarah H. M. (Knowles), 1902, 1927, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Croll, Albert Ivins, 1902 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - DeFriez family, 1918-1981, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Easton family, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Feyerabend family (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Freeman family, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Gardiner family, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Gibson family, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Grant, Ulysses S., 1885 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Grantlin, Christine Easton, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Gray, Pauline (DeFriez), n.d. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Gregory, Dudley Stevens, and family, 1920-1958, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Gregory, George Dudley, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Gregory, Helen Lee (Stevens), 1888-1898, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Gross family, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Hahn family, 1910 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Hayes family, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Hogaboom family, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Howe and Loomis families, 1882, 1957-1959,n.d. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Ivins Family, ca.1857 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Josephson family, 1978, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Kling family, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Knauss family - Group shots, 1901-1987, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 9-11)
    - Knauss family - Annotated and Coat of Arms, 1898-1981, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Knauss family genealogy (Vol. III): Negatives (Box 32, Folder 13-18)
    - Knauss, Amanda - Bill, 1987, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Knauss, Charles - Donald, 1878-1985, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Knauss, Edgar - Edwin, 1919-1986, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Knauss, Elaine - Erich, 1967, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Knauss, Ernest and Pauline, and family (Box 32, Folder 23-24)
    - Knauss, Eugen and Hermine, and family, 1985, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Knauss, Frederick, 1978, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Knauss, Gotthilf and Julia (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Knauss, Gottlob and Sophie, and family, 1910, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Knauss, Gustav, 1899-1928, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Knauss, Heinrich - Helen, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Knauss, Herman and family, 1923-1982 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Knauss, Howard, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Knauss, Jim - John, 1898-1984, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Knauss, Lloyd - Louis, 1959-1978, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Knauss, Manfred - Peter, 1945-1987, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Knauss, Richard - Sophie, 1986, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Knauss, Walter, and families, 1921-1968, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Knauss, William F. and Emma, and family, 1928-1955, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 1-2)
    - Kneeland, Yale (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Knight, John, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Knowles family, 1906, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 4-5)
    - Krause family, 1986-1987, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Krumnow family, 1987, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Lee family, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Loomis family (see Howe and Loomis family) (Box -, Folder -)
    - Lund family (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Mace family, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Martel family, 1987-1992 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Martinez-Cardeza family, 1880-1890, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Martinez-Cardeza, Isabella (Hammond) (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Merriam family, 1984-1986 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Newbury family, 1980-1981 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Newell, Harriet (engraving), n.d. (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Neuschütz, Eduard, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Nichols family, 1982-1985, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 12-13)
    - Nickse family, 1921-1963, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 14-17)
    - Olson family, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Parmelee family (Box 33, Folder 19-20)
    - Penfield, Sarah, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Pond family, 1981, 1990, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Poynter family, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Reed, Dorothea (Stevens) and family, 1930-1990, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Reuman(n) family - Group shots, 1899-1986, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Reuman(n), Arthur - Clara, 1956-1986 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Reuman(n), Evelyn - Herman, 1888-1925, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Reuman(n), Jeffrey - Paul, 1925-1986, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Reuman(n), Robert - Steven, 1983-1986, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Reuman(n), Ted, 1934-1951, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Rosenblum family, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Rowell, Willie F., friend of Albert C. Stevens (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Sandell family, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Schmidt, Sophie Pauline, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Schrauth family, 1959, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Scruggs family, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Smith family - Group shots, family coat of arms, 1877, 1911 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Smith, Augustus Allen and Mary K. (Kelham), 1864, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Smith, Major Burley (1778-1855), n.d. (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Smith, Lydia Lee (Knight), 1890s, 1893 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Smith, Lydia Lee (Knight), n.d. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Snyder family, 1935, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Sommer family, 1924-1930 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Speer family, 1922-1955, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 4-Mar)
    - Speer family, 1894, 1926 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Sproule family, 1887, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Sproule, Andrew M., ca.1894, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 7-Jun)
    - Sproule, Anna Rebecca (Hammond) (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Stevens/Croll family group shots, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Stevens, Albert Clark, 1885-1919, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Stevens, Albert Gallatin and Sarah Caroline (Greene) (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Stevens, Alden Sprague (1795-1874), n.d. (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Stevens, Edward Webster Dann (b. 1926) and family, 1967-1990, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Stevens, Eva Loomis Howe (1892-1988), n.d., 1963-1970 (Box 34, Folder 13-14)
    - Stevens, Eva Loomis Howe (1892-1988), n.d. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - -- with Eva Grove Loomis Howe (1856-1944), n.d. (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - -- with Robert Sproule Stevens (1888-1968), n.d. (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Stevens, Frederick Charles (1856-1916), 1876, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Stevens, Frederick Charles Jr. (1890-1965) and family, 1899-1911, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Stevens, Frederick Charles III (b. 1924) and family, 1925-1979, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Stevens, Frederick Plummer (1810-1866), n.d. (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Stevens, Isabelle Cardeza (Sproule) (1858-1943), 1890s, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Stevens, Jane Eleanor (Knauss), ca.1930-1948 (Box 34, Folder 20-21)
    - Stevens, Jane Eleanor (Knauss), ca.1930 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Stevens, Marian (1885-1974), 1910, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Stevens, Pauline Croll (1885-1936), 1906-1920, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Stevens, Pauline Croll (1885-1936), 1902-1911, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Stevens, Pauline Croll (1885-1936), 1922 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - #NAME?, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - --with Grace Lawrence Croll (DeFriez) (1885- 1969), 1890-1894, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Stevens, Robert Croll (b. 1924), 1924-1938, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 26-27)
    - Stevens, Robert Croll (b. 1924), 1925-1932, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Stevens, Robert Croll (b. 1924), n.d. (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Stevens, Robert Croll (b. 1924), 1950s-1960s (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Stevens, Robert Croll (b. 1924): Pencil drawing, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Stevens, Robert Croll (b. 1924): Hackley School & Football, 1936-1937 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Stevens, Robert Croll (b. 1924): Andover portrait, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Stevens, Robert Croll (b. 1924): His children, 1973-1986, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Stevens, Robert Croll (b. 1924): His children, 1965 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Stevens, Robert Croll (see below for snapshots) (Box -, Folder -)
    - Stevens, Robert Hastings (1802-1889), n.d. (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Stevens, Robert Hastings (b. 1907) and family, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Stevens, Robert Sproule (1888-1968), 1890-1954, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 33-34)
    - Stevens, Robert Sproule (1888-1968), 1919? (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - --with "Mamie" Sophie Oliver, 1889 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - --with Eva Loomis Howe Stevens (1892-1988), n.d. (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - --with Frederick C. Stevens, Jr. (1890-1965), 1901, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - --with grandmother (?), ca.1888 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - #NAME?, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Stevens, Robert Wadleigh Smith (1824-1893), ca.1891 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Stevens, Sarah H. (Smith) (d. 1889), n.d. (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Stiegman family, 1905-1936, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Stockinger family, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Stoothoff family, 1973-1986, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Theurer family, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Williams family, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - Windmüller family, 1959-1964, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Zimmerman family, 1984, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - VIII-B. Family Homes and Other Locations
    - Family Homes and Residences
      - Bahret family, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Barrows, William N. and Kate E. (Briggs), 1977, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Blackburne/Sharpe family (?), 1954 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Clark, Stephen, 1826-1952 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Croll family, 1901-1980, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Croll family, n.d. (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Knauss family, 1900-1942, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 7-Jun)
      - Knauss Bros. Factories, 1925, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Knowles family, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Lee family, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Martin, Mary Cogswell (Smith), n.d. (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Smith, Augustus Allen, 1910, 1977, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Smith, Augustus Williston, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Smith, Burley, 1910, 1977, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Speer family, 1987, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Stevens Memorial Library, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Stevens, Albert G. and Sarah C. (Greene) (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Stevens, Albert G. and Sarah C. (Greene), ca.1867 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Stevens, Alden Sprague and Ascha (Smith) (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Stevens, Eva Howe: House at the George Junior Republic, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - Stevens, Frederick C. and Belle C. (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Stevens, Frederick Plummer, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Stevens, Frederick Plummer, ca.1867 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Stevens, Robert Sproule and family, 1964, 1970, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Stevens, Robert W. Smith and Mary (Smith), 1977, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - General Locations
      - Attica, NY: Attica Historical Calendar, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Bad Wimpfen, Germany, 1987, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Buffalo, NY, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - Endersbach, Germany (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Kansas, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - Unidentified houses/places, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - Unidentified houses/places, 1912 (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - Wolfsölden, Germany, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - VIII-C. Frederick C. Stevens Vacation Photographs
    - Around the world: F.C. Stevens and F.C. Stevens, Jr.:, 1911 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Grand Canyon and Yellowstone: Frederick and Belle Stevens family (negatives only), 1912 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - VIII-D. Robert Croll Stevens Snapshots and Photos
    - Washington, D.C. and Mt. Vernon, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Trip around the world, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Grayling, Michigan, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Hackley School, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Postcard of Hackley School, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Bermuda, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - School and NY World's Fair, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Trip west: Grand Canyon, Yellowstone Park, etc., 1939 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Nantucket, MA, 1941 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Massachusetts: Harvard, Andover, Chatham, 1941-1942 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Harvard friends, 1942, n.d. (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Frederick C. Stevens III wedding, Buffalo, NY, 1947 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Honeymoon: Maine and Nantucket, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - New York: Ithaca, Attica, Rochester, Adirondacks (Box 35, Folder 32-33)
    - Negatives from red photo album (box 36-8), n.d. (1930s) (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Various and unidentified (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Photos at and of Stromberg-Carlson, 1950s-1960s (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Snapshot of Knauss relatives (Eugen Knauss, Hermine Knauss, Jeanne Gross [Knauss], Helene Schmidt [Knauss]), n.d. (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - VIII-E. Photograph Albums
    - ? Cons Smith-Stevens-Sproule family album n.d.
      - Eva Loomis Howe Stevens album, 1963-1965 (Box 35, Folder 36)
      - Pauline Croll Stevens album, 1900-1906 (Box 35, Folder 37)
      - Pauline Croll Stevens album, 1906-1911 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Pauline Croll Stevens album, 1908-1923 (Box 37, Folder -)
      - Pauline Croll Stevens album, 1911-1914 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Pauline Croll Stevens album, 1913 (Box 37, Folder -)
      - Pauline Croll Stevens album, 1920-1925 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Pauline Croll Stevens album, 1924-1931 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Pauline Croll Stevens album, 1925-1928 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Pauline Croll Stevens album, 1928-1932 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Pauline Croll Stevens album, 1931-1932 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Pauline Croll Stevens album, n.d. (ca.1930s) (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Robert Croll Stevens album: Trip around the world, 1935-1936 (Box 37, Folder -)
  - VIII-F. Postcard Collections
    - Postcard album: John & Agnes Blackburne, 1905-1909 (Box 28, Folder -)
    - (Helen) Pauline Croll Stevens albums
      - Postcard album, 1908-1910 (Box 28, Folder -)
      - Postcard album: Germany, France, Italy, opera singers, New York, New Jersey, Massachusetts, Canada, California, Connecticut, Monaco, Pennsylvania, Florida, England, Bahamas, Algeria, Colorado, South Carolina, Washington DC, Vermont, Jamaica, Maryland, Missouri, New Hampshire, 1910, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Postcard album: Massachusetts, New York, army shots (World War I?), Presidents Taft & Wilson, Canada, Florida, southern plantations, Virginia, Texas, Mexico, New Hampshire, Maine, China, Hungary, Bethlehem, England, France, Italy, artwork, Pennsylvania (Box 38, Folder -)
      - Postcard album: Brazil, Gibraltar, Egypt, Yemen, Sri Lanka (Ceylon), Madura, India, Myanmar (Burma), Pakistan, Malaysia, China, Singapore, Russia (Box 38, Folder -)
      - Postcard album: St. Thomas, Brazil, Uruguay, Argentina, Bolivia, Trinidad, Cuba, Barbados, Puerto Rico, Haiti, Bahamas, Bermuda, National Parks: Rocky Mountain, Yellowstone Park, Glacier, Yosemite, Bryce Canyon; California, Utah, n.d. (Box 38, Folder -)
      - Postcard album: Florida, New York, Germany, France, New Mexico, Massachusetts, Virginia, Canada, England, Algeria, California, steam ships, Bermuda, Michigan, South Carolina, Vermont, Pennsylvania, Washington DC, New Jersey, Georgia, Oklahoma, Mississippi (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Postcard album: New York, Arizona, California, ships, France, New Mexico, Pennsylvania, Italy, Canada, Rhode Island, Bahamas, Massachusetts, Vermont, Washington DC, Ireland, New Jersey, Algeria, Panama, England, Connecticut, Austria (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - VIII-G. Other Images: Gravestones, Engravings, Prints
    - Gravestones/Cemeteries (Box 39, Folder 3-Feb)
    - Gravestones/Cemeteries (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Yankee Clipper and Dixie Clipper (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Engravings and prints, 1847, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Series IX. Audio/Visual Materials
  - Audio/Visual records of the Trip Around The World (Robert Sproule Stevens, Pauline Croll Stevens, Robert Croll Stevens), September 5, 1935 - February 9, 1936
    (Robert Sproule Stevens, Pauline Croll Stevens, Robert Croll Stevens), September 5, 1935 - February 9, 1936
    - Original 16mm film (3 reels), n.d. (Box 73)
    - VHS videotape of the 16mm film (unedited), n.d. (Box 73)
    - Box with master-edited VHS videotape and bound book (transcripts of letters/diaries pertaining to the trip), 1992 (Box 73)
    - Master-edited audio cassette tape, 1992 (Box 73)
    - DVD-766 – “Around the World, September 1935 to February 1936, with Pauline’s sketches” (Box 92)
  - VHS Videocassette Tapes
    - Oakwood Cemetary Historical Walking Tour, Parsons, Ks., 7-Oct-90 (Box 73)
    - Belmont Avenue Historical Walking Tour, Parsons, Ks., 19-May-91 (Box 73)
    - "Dairy Farming, A Lost Legacy - Maplewood Farms," Robert Reed Chudy's interview of Richard Stevens on the economy of dairy farming, 38 minutes, 1997 (Box 73)
    - Papers relating to RCS's acquisition of "A Lost Legacy", 1998 (Box 73)
  - Audio Cassette Tapes
    - Interview with Michael Snyder Stafford, n.d. (Box 73)
    - Manfred Albrecht, M.D. translates Knauss letters, n.d. (Box 73)
    - Interview with Rufus Newton Barrows, n.d. (Box 73)
    - Interview with Eva Loomis Howe Stevens, 29-Apr-74 (Box 73)
    - Interview with Dr. Robert H. Stevens; Interview with Dr. A. Ivins C. DeFriez, May 30, 1975; June 7, 1975 (Box 73)
    - Interview with Mrs. Frederick C.Stevens Jr. (Aunt Dorothea), 19-Jan-76 (Box 73)
    - Interview with Gertrude Kelham Smith Snyder, May-76 (Box 73)
    - Interview with Dr. A. Ivins C. DeFriez, 24-May-80 (Box 73)
    - Robert Nickse and his mother Louise Knauss Nickse, Tapes I and II, May 18, 1981; May 18, 1984 (Box 73)
    - Herman Knauss Recollections, 1-Mar-84 (Box 73)
    - Interview with Lindsay Pond, Trip to Wales, Aug-86 (Box 73)
    - Interview with Rev. Albrecht Binetsch; Interview with Luise Speer, May 18, 1987; May 30, 1987 (Box 73)
    - Jane Alden Stevens reminiscences on her Knauss grandparents, 19-Jun-87 (Box 73)
    - Box of 3 tapes: interviews of Barb, Bob, and Jean (Betty) Pond., April 8-9, 1989 (Box 73)
    - Mayrana Harding, Parsons, Ks., May-91 (Box 73)
    - Interview with Claude Easterly, retired newspaperman of Denison, TX, on early history of Denison and the MK & T Rwy. (2 tapes), 12-May-93 (Box 73)
    - Interview with Bob Wall in Parsons, Ks. on George Carr, 17-May-93 (Box 73)
  - CD's, DVD's
    - CD-9 – “A Five Year Diary", by Marian Stevens (copy of "Line A Day” transcript) (Box 92)
    - DVD-767 – Trip to Tobago, March 4 to 21, 1954 (Box 92)
    - DVD-768 – San Francisco to Christmas, 1966 (Box 92)
    - DVD-769 – 1971 Slide Show, 1971 (Box 92)
    - DVD-770 – 1972 Family Events, 1972 (Box 92)
    - DVD-771 – 1972 Rome-Israel-Greece, 1972 (Box 92)
    - DVD-772 – Ireland, Part 1 Belfast to Adare, May 23-30, 2004 (Box 92)
    - DVD-773 – Ireland, Part 2 Adare to Dublin, May 30-June 7, 2004 (Box 92)
    - DVD-774 – Passage of Lewis and Clark Part 1, October 12-27, 2005 (Box 92)
    - DVD-775 – Passage of Lewis and Clark Part 2, October 15-27, 2005 (Box 92)
    - DVD-776 – Katy Days, Parsons, Kansas, May 25 to 31, 2005 (Box 92)
    - DVD-777 – Jane K. Stevens, 80th Birthday (Box 92)
    - DVD-778 – Memorial Service [Jane Knauss Stevens], February 23, 2008 (Box 92)
    - DVD-779 – William C. Stevens: His First 49 Years (Box 92)
    - DVD-931 – Stevens Family Movies, 1930-1940 (Box 93)
    - DVD-932 – Part 1 - 1949 to 1953, 1949-1953 (Box 93)
    - DVD-933 – Part 2 - 1953 to 1956, 1953-1956 (Box 93)
    - DVD-934 – Part 3 - 1956 to 1958, 1956-1958 (Box 93)
    - DVD-935 – Part 4 - 1959 to 1960, 1959-1960 (Box 93)
    - DVD-936 – House Remodeling, May to Sept. 1954 (Box 93)
    - DVD-937 – Watkins Glen Grand Prix, 1954, 1955 and 1956 (Box 93)
    - DVD-938 – Trains on the Hamilton, Ontario, "Wye.", May 1955 (Box 93)
    - DVD-939 – Trip to Europe, Part 1 – Germany, 1959 (Box 93)
    - DVD-940 – Trip to Europe, Part 2 - Norway and London, 1959 (Box 93)
    - DVD-941 – Vacation Trip and Fire, 1960 and 1961 (Box 93)
    - DVD-942 – Trip to Jamaica, March/April 1961 (Box 93)
    - DVD-943 – Bushnell's Basin Barn Fire: (also see above), 1961 (Box 93)
    - DVD-944 – Family Events, 1961 and 1962 (Box 93)
    - DVD-945 – Family Events, 1963 and 1964 (Box 93)
    - DVD-946 – Durango to Silverton Railway, 1964-1967 (Box 93)
    - DVD-947 – Antigua; Home; Baseball; Nantucket; World's Fair and Florida, 1965 (Box 93)
    - DVD-948 – Flights of Gemini III and Ranger IX, March 23 and 27, 1965 (Box 93)
    - DVD-949 – Part 1 - Trip around the USA (To San Simeon), 1967 (Box 93)
    - DVD-950 – Part 2 - Trip around the USA (To Home), 1967 (Box 93)
    - DVD-951 – Our Family, 1967 and 1968 (Box 93)
    - DVD-952 – Eagle Lake; Barbados; Home and Barbara (German friend), 1969 and 1970 (Box 93)
    - DVD-953 – Family Events, 1973 (Box 93)
    - DVD-954 – Part 1 - Alaska Experience to Denali, Aug. 30-Sept. 18, 1994 (Box 93)
    - DVD-955 – Part 2 - Alaska Experience, Aug. 30-Sept. 18, 1994 (Box 93)
    - DVD-956 – Part 1 - African Adventure - To Cape Town, 1998 (Box 93)
    - DVD-957 – Part 2 - African Adventure - To Mala Mala, 1998 (Box 93)
    - DVD-958 – Part 3 - African Adventure - To Victoria Falls, 1998 (Box 93)
    - DVD-959 – Part 4 - African Adventure - To Impalila, 1998 (Box 93)
    - DVD-960 – Part 5 - African Adventure - To Home, 1998 (Box 93)
    - DVD-961 – Part 1 - French Adventure - To Chalon, 1998 (Box 93)
    - DVD-962 – Part 2 - French Adventure - To Dijon, 1998 (Box 93)
    - DVD-963 – Part 3 - French Adventure - To Paris and Home, 1998 (Box 93)
    - DVD-964 – Part 1 - Wedding Anniversary Celebration, 1999 (Box 93)
    - DVD-965 – Part 2 - Germany, - July 29 to Aug. 4, 1999 (Box 93)
    - DVD-966 – Part 3 and 4 - Czech Rep. and Belgium, Aug. 4-13, 1999 (Box 93)
    - DVD-967 – Camp Encampments and Hurricane Floyd, 1999 (Box 93)
    - DVD-968 – Part 1 - Switzerland and Italy - To JFK to Interlaken, 2002 (Box 93)
    - DVD-969 – Part 2 - Switzerland and Italy - To Lausanne, 2002 (Box 93)
    - DVD-970 – Part 3 - Switzerland and Italy - To Zermatt, 2002 (Box 93)
    - DVD-971 – Part 4 - Switzerland and Italy - To Venice, 2002 (Box 93)
    - DVD-972 – Part 5 - Switzerland and Italy - To Florence, 2002 (Box 93)
    - DVD-973 – Christmas (2002) and Graduations (2003), 2002, 2003 (Box 93)
    - DVD-974 – Bob's 80th Birthday Party - Freeman's Picture of the Party, Jan. 2, 2004 (Box 93)
    - DVD-975 – Part 1 - London: "The Play's the Thing", May 10-23, 2004 (Box 93)
    - DVD-976 – Part 2 - London: "The World of Art", May 10-23, 2004 (Box 93)
    - DVD-977 – Ft. Ticonderoga: National Fife and Drum Corp Muster, 2005 (Box 93)
    - DVD-978 – Jane K. Stevens: Frank H.T. Rhodes Award, Oct. 13, 2006 (Box 93)
    - DVD-988 – Niagara Falls, poem, n.d. (Box 93)
  - Other Formats
    - Recording Tape: Robert Sproule Stevens's Autobiography 1 (Box 73)
    - Recording Tape: Robert Sproule Stevens's Autobiography 2 (Box 73)
    - Microfilm: RSS transcripts 1824-1893, Index, 1960-62 (?) (Box 73)
    - Microfilm: RSS transcripts 1824-1893, 1962-65, 1972-73 (?) (Box 73)
    - F. C. Stevens transcriptions of documents (File C), 1886-1888 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Contents of File C.: \Cornell \ 1880-1887.CON (Box 88, Folder 2)